《越狱》前情回顾
Previously on prison break
我保证 放心吧
it will work out. You have my word.Be careful.
简会照顾你的
Jane's gonna look after you.
嘿
Hey.
我有个妹妹 15年来没和她说过一句话
I have a sister, I haven't talked to in 15 years.
你认为她过的很好?
You think she's better off for it?
布鲁斯?
Bruce?
我说过我们不能用这个号码
I know we said not to use this number,
但我只想知道你一切都好
but I just needed to know you were okay.
是你
It was you.
你在说什么 莎拉?
What are you talking about, Sara?
我有三个字要对你说
I got three words for you.
马上跑
We gotta run.
我想要自首
I want to turn myself in
但我有个要求
But I got one condition
你妻子一小时前被释放了
Your wife was released an hour ago
她马上就会到这里来的
She'll be here soon.
只要你完成交易
Just hold up your end of the deal.
我会帮你抓住斯科菲尔德的
I'll get you Scofield.
一位国家安全局的分析师同意了我们的计划
An nsa analyst sympathetic to our cause got
他手上有一段录音 是在你被确认杀了特伦斯 斯蒂德曼
his hands on a phone conversation the president had
两周后 总统和特伦斯
with Terrence Steadman two weeks after you
进行的通话录音
supposedly killed him.
24小时后 唐克雷蒂州长死了
24 hours later, Tancredi is dead,
那分析师也失踪了
the analyst is missing
而且白宫的录音序列
and the White House Echelon tapes
也从主机上被删了
have been deleted from the mainframe
这个录音 有我们想要的一切
There's a tape, gives us everything we need.
如果我们找到的话 林肯将重获自由
Linc will be set free if we find it.
这里有你需要的东西
You have something here.
肯定有许多人不希望你得到
There are gonna be a lot of people wish you didn't, but you do.
你认为是一段对话?
conversation?
一个他们不想让我们听到的对话
One they don't want us to hear.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
开始吧
Let's do it.
上帝啊
oh, my god.
对
Yeah.
帕托塞克 ...
Patoshik...
死了
dead.
富兰克林...
Franklin
被监禁并提供帮助我们
incarcerated and assisting with
找到斯科菲尔德和布伦斯
the capture of Scofield and Burrows.
你和他用什么做的交易?
What exactly is the protocol with that?
我会搞定的
I'll handle that.
我们成功一半了 先生们
We're at the halfway mark, people.
布伦斯 斯科菲尔德...
Burrows, Scofield...
巴格威尔 苏克雷--
Bagwell, Sucre--
他们还在逃
they're still out there.
我得到了一个...
Now, I heard a report came in from...
从墨西哥来的情报
Mexico.
苏克雷 费尔南多
Fernando Sucre
差点在伊斯塔帕机场被捕
was almost apprehended at the airport in Ixtapa.
抱歉
Excuse me.
请到我办公室来
Office, please.
你到这里来干什么?
What the hell are you doing here?
我来要我的那笔该死的钱
I came for my damn money.
什么?
Your what?
看看，赏金是怎么回事
The Patoshik reward money.
有人得到了那笔赏钱
See, how a reward works is, someone gets rewarded the money,
可我才是那个找到那个疯子
and since I'm the one who bloodhounded haywire
应该得到赏钱的人
the money gets rewarded to me.
你跑到我的办公室来... 如果你回过我的任何一个电话
You come to my office...
我不用必须到这里来
if you'd returned any of my calls, I wouldn't have had to.
我们说好的
We had a deal.
我们说好的是你尽量别被人发现
The deal was that you stay under the radar.
你做的很好啊 光头?
这里到处都是联邦探员
No, this is an office full of federal agents
他们都看见你的长相了
who now have all seen your face.
我才不在乎
Yeah, I don't care what they see.
如果你不给我钱的话
Hell, if you don't pay up
那我就脱了裤子从这里出去
I'll go out there and drop trou.
帕托塞克死了 你这个混蛋
Patoshik died, you stupid son of a bitch.
而且还有书面报告
There's paperwork involved
你当然能拿到你的钱
Of course you're going to get the money.
但你要耐心点
But you're gonna have to be patient.
如果你再...
And if you ever...
踏进我的办公室
come in my office again,
你不但看不到现金
you'll not only never see the cash
而且肯定见不到下一次日出了
you'll never see another sunrise.
现在我们还要嚷嚷
你将要得到的那笔钱吗?
now, are we gonna keep crying about money you've already got coming to you?
或者你还想多挣点?
Or do you want to make some more?
我听着呢
I'm listening.
去过墨西哥吗?
Ever been to Mexico?
我们把这个交给媒体
We give this thing to the press
政府将会质疑它
the government's gonna discredit it
就像怀疑我们录制的那个录像一样
just like they did with the tape we made
那么...
Okay.
那我们拿它怎么办?
So what do we do with it?
父亲说管理部门里还有
ad said there are still people in the administration
和他一起工作的人能帮助我们
that he was working with.
如果把这给他们最终会找到
If we give the tape to them, they'll finally have
无可辩驳的罪证让卡罗琳.莱娜斯垮台
the smoking gun they need to bring Caroline Reynolds down.
但他们将发布这里面的内容...
But they'll release the tape...
而不是我们
not us.
她怎么能怀疑她任命的人呢
And how can she discredit her own appointees? Sure.
我们唯一能证明我无罪
We're gonna give the only thing that can exonerate me
的东西交给政府里工作的某个人?
to someone who works for the government?
那个陷害我的政府?!
The same government that set me up?
我们必须找到我们信任的人
We'll have to find someone we can trust
诚实的人
someone honest.
简 菲利普斯
Jane Phillips
她知道谁能帮助我们
She'll know someone that can help us
她和我父亲一起工作 并照顾LJ
She worked with dad; she's watching LJ
我信任她 迈克尔
I trust her, Michael.
让她去找我们需要的人
She'll do it; she'll find someone.
好吧 但愿你是对的
Well, I hope you're right.
因为这是我们最后一击
Because this is our last shot.
这个很不错
This'll do you right
这是雷明登700狙击步枪
She's a remington 700.
她很准吗?
She a clean shot?
就像个女人 一向很准
Like a good woman, she does not stray.
不锈钢枪管
Varmint, stainless
重量级口径 175 发空心瞄准
steel fluted barrel, heavyweight caliber, 175-grain hollow point.
那个箱子我也要了
- I'll take the case, too.
这是秘密渠道来的...
- She's a throw-in.
序列号已清除了
Serial numbers have been cleaned.
为了摆脱弹道，枪膛已经被刮花了
Chamber's been scraped to throw off ballistics
以防万一你不只是
just in case you're not,
用它来打罐头
you know, shooting at tin cans.
我的猎物可比这大多了
No, I'm hunting bigger game than that.
没有任何消息
Radio silence.
我只是不知道
Look, I just don't know
他多少时间看一次这个
how often he checks this thing, all right?
看上去他不怎么看啊!
Well, it seems not that often
你已经发了三条消息了
considering you've posted three messages.
我开始怀疑我需不需要你了
I'm starting to wonder why I need you at all.
帮你找到斯科菲尔德
To get Scofield. What?
那我们在这里做什么?
hat are we doing here?
我们能发消息 但斯科菲尔德
Well, I can type, and Scofield can't see who's sending him the messages.
真的会上钩吗?
Well, you know what,
他能察觉任何很小的事物
he's gonna see whatever little rent-a-fed cops
和你们给他设的陷阱
that you guys have set up whatever place you guys are gonna set up to meet him.
现在你和我都知道这小子有多聪明了?
Now, you and i both know how smart this kid is, right?
当然比你聪明 考虑到
Clearly smarter than you
你现在已经被监禁了
considering you're the one who's wearing bright orange.
是的
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
像他这么机敏的人
Fish is not gonna peek his little white ass
不会贸然现身
out from any rock that he's hiding
除非有熟人出现在他面前
unless he sees a failiar face.
一个... 那人就是你吧?
A famili... and that's your face, right?
是啊 那你就别装了
Yeah, you're damn straight it is,
你说苏克雷...
so don't pretend you said Sucre...
你听到了他们谈论的网站!
- You overheard him telling Sucre about a web site!
别装做你不需要我似的
- Don't pretend like you don't need me.
你真的听到了?
- You overheard something?
他是一个童子军...
- Look, he's a boy scout, he...
这个能行的?!
I don't see...  he helps, okay?!
如果你有点耐心 他会回消息的!
If you have a little bit of patience, he will hit me back!
我是唯一能帮助你家庭的人
I'm the only one in the world right now helping your family.
我的家庭和你无关
- I help my family, okay? - So do I.
我释放了你的妻子
I'm the one that got Kacee released,
让你的女儿接受治疗
I'm the one that gets Dede medical care,
我还允许你探望他们
I'm the one that allows you to visit them,
我也可以夺走一切
and I'm the one that can take it away.
你知道
Well, you know what, it looks like
这对我们都好 不是吗?
we both need each other, doesn't it?
是吗? 在协议达成前
Do we? So I am gonna hold up my end of the bargain,
我有我的权利?
and guess what?
你也有自己的
You hold up yours.
现在给我滚开
Now, get off my back.
你会得到你想要的
You can get what you want.
只要给我 我想要的
Just give me what I want.
找到斯科菲尔德
Give me Scofield.
你好?
- hello?
伙计
- Hey, buddy.
爸爸?
Dad?
是我
Yeah, it's me.
你还好吗?
How you holding up?
好 你呢?
Okay. How about you?
一切都好
Good.
好
我... 我想你
I, uh... i miss you.
嗯 我也是
Yeah, me, too.
我不知道你有简的电话号码
I didn't know you had Jane's number.
嗯 你们分开的时候我们交换了号码
Yeah, well, uh, we exchanged numbers when you guys split.
你从来没打过
You never called.
对 我没有...
No. Yeah...
对不起 一直以来都处于危险之中
I'm sorry, it's been, uh, it's been dangerous.
你知道? 有一点危险
- You know? A little dangerous.
不过没 没关系
- It's-it's okay.
LJ
听着 我知道我以前说过
uh, listen, I know I've said this before,
但我觉得我们已经找到些什么
but I think we've found something
可以最终将这个东西
that's finally gonna put this stuff
抛之于我们脑后
behind us.
等时机到了 安全了
When it's good, when it's safe,
我会来接你的
I'm going to come and get you.
你 我 还有你叔叔...
You, me, your uncle...
爸爸
- daD.
嗯?
- Yeah?
我想要你结束这一切
但是...我又上学了
but... I'm in school again.
用的假名字 但是还在上学 你知道吗?
Under a fake name, but it's still school, you know?
我的意思是 虽然不太一样 但是跟
I mean, it's not the same
我长期拥有的家很接近
but it's the closest thing to a home I've had in a long time.
我....我猜...
I... I guess...
我猜我只是说...现在
I guess I'm just saying that...
一段时间...
for now, for-for a while...
我只是想呆在一个
I just want to stay in one place,
正常点的地方
have something normal.
好 我... 我懂
Yeah, yeah, I... Yeah, yeah, I...
我...
I, uh...
要跟简说说话
I need to speak with Jane.
好
Okay.
我爱你 爸爸
I love you, dad.
我也爱你 儿子
I love you, too, son.
韦伯斯特先生
Mr. Webster.
不好意思 让您久等了
Sorry to keep you waiting.
没关系 医生
Ah, it's no problem, doc.
我 我想告诉您 非常感谢您
I just, uh, wanted to tell you how much
这么快就能见我
I appreciate you seeing me on such short notice.
那是我应该做的
That's what I'm here for.
好
Good.
因为我有一些东西
'Cause I got a few things
需要从我箱子里取出来
I need to get off my chest.
再见 简
See you, Jane.
库珀 格林?
Cooper Green?
前代理司法部长
Former deputy attorney general.
在华盛顿 芝加哥和纽约之间奔波
Splits his time between DC, Chicago and Nnew York,
简说他永远是爸爸的同盟
我们找到了他 就有机会了
We find him, we got a shot.
LJ怎么样了?
How is LJ?
他很好
He's doing all right.
库珀 格林办公室
Cooper Green's office.
对不起 格林先生现在很忙
I'm sorry, Mr. Green isn't available at this time.
拜托 我有很重要的事情
Please, this is very important.
告诉他我有关于
Just tell him I have some information
奥尔多 布伦斯的儿子的消息
regarding the sons of Aldo Burrows.
奥尔多 布伦斯?
- Aldo Burrows?
对
- Yes.
他和格林先生过去经常合作
He and Mr. Green used to work together.
请稍等 我想办法联络他
Please hold. I'l try to reach him.
她正在联络他
你好
格林先生
- Mr. Green
我是迈克尔·斯科菲尔德 知道我是谁吗?
this is Michael Scofield.　- Do you know who I am?
当然 我认识你父亲
- Of course. I knew your father.
我也知道他发生什么事了
And I know what happened to him.I'm sorry.
对不起 他是一个好人 总是设法做好事
He was a good man trying to do good things.
我们也是
Well, so are we.
我们有些东西
We have something.
录音
- The tape.
你们已经听了
- You've heard of it.
我知道很多人
ell, I know a lot of people
都在找它
have been looking for it.
录音上有些什么?
What's on the tape?
如果你想知道的话
If you want to find out
在艾伯特公园的西南角
there's a bronze statue of a mammoth
有个猛犸的铜雕像
at the southwest corner of ebert park.
我要你在一个小时之内到那达那里
I need you there in an hour.
你有蓝色西装吗
Do you have a blue suit?
有　穿上 打红色领带
- Yes.- Wear it, and a red tie.
这样的话 我们才知道你是谁
That way, we'll know who you are.
准备好了吗?
ready?
嗯
Yeah.
祝你好运
Good luck.
会成功的
This will work.
你认为会吗?
You think?
你好 莎拉
Hello, Sara.
你知道你最终会出现的
I figured you'd show up eventually.
你看上去不错 布鲁斯
You look good, Bruce.
在我爸爸的牺牲之下你干得不错
You've done well for yourself at my father's expense.
我与你父亲无关
I had nothing to do with your fath.
你父亲是被人谋杀的 那个人就是你
Your father was murdered. By you.
然后你又试图杀我
And then you tried to have me killed.Don't...
不...你怎么能那样说?
how can you say that?
我的线路被监听了 他们能够听到你的话
My line was tapped, and they heard you tell
告诉我你在那个公用电话亭
me that you were at that pay phone.
莎拉 我知道你的家庭 我的一生
Sara, I've known your family my entire life.
这更让你的背叛变得令人恶心
Which makes your betrayal disgusting.
为了它的价值 我一直在受折磨
For what it's worth, I've been tortured already
但是没用
It didn't work.
我不用向你为自己辩护 莎拉
I shouldn't have to defend myself to you, Sara.
如果你不相信我
If you can't trust me,
那么我能做的一切只能是祝你好运
then all I can do is just wish you luck.
走
Go.
在你开始之前
look, before you get started,
我要为你节约点时间 领导
I'm gonna save you some time here, jefe.
我曾经为你扮演老鼠 就那样了
I played rat for you once, and that was it.
我现在受保护了
I got protection now.
我让这儿的顶级破车樱桃挑选衣服
I let the top bangers in here cherry pick the laundry--
干净的被单 全新的短裤 因此
clean sheets, new shorts--
你动不了我了
and for that, I'm untouchable.
所以威胁到你想要的一切 家
So threaten all you want, homes.
小子 你要做什么
Yo, man, what are you going to do?
你好像不常打网球啊 曼澈
You don't look like you play too much tennis, Manche.
这个可能
This is probably
比你的速度快
more you　speed.
娱乐中心
Entertainment center.
宽屏等离子
Wide-screen plasma.
桌球
Pinball.
扑克牌桌
Poker table.
小子 这到底是什么?
Yo, man, what the hell is this?
你的将来
在坎卡基最小的安全矫正中心
At Kankakee minimum security correctional center,
比枕头更软的东西就只有保卫了
where the only thing softer than　the pillows are the guards.
我并不是来恐吓的你的
I didn't come here to threaten.
我的意思是 在驴子要为了方糖努力工作的时候
I mean, why whip the mule when
为什么要打他?
he'll work even harder for a sugar cube?
那些狐狸从这里逃出去的路线
The same connections that
我也可以
got this fox out of the river so quick,
给你
well, I can use them for you, too.
我需要知道的一切
All I need to know is where down in Mexico
都在你的堂兄苏克雷已经去了的墨西哥
your cousin Sucre is headed.
看 宝贝 快看!
Look, mami, look!
我告诉过你 这是美洲驼!
I told you. Llamas!
我认为这是羊驼.
I think those are alpacas.
我就是这个意思 美洲羊驼
That's what I said, a pack-a llamas.
费尔南多!
Fernando!
婶婶
Auntie?
我的好孩子
My sister's baby boy.
见到你太高兴了
It's so good to see you.
这是玛丽克鲁斯
This is my Maricruz...
...这是我们的孩子
...and this is our child.
我们在这里安全吗?
e will be safe here?
当然了 这儿现在就是你的家了
Yes.This is your home now.
医生 我想说的是...
what I'm trying to tell you, doc,
我觉得自己的一生...
is I just feel like
就像是 在铁轨上的一枚硬币
I've been a penny on the train tracks my entire life.
而那辆'ole Union Pacific(列车名称)  每天都会开过
And that 'ole union pacific just keeps on coming,
来来回回 从我身上辗过
every day, back and forth,
但我不会失去 光泽
ust running me down, running me over, but I will not flatten.
我不会失去光泽
I will not flatten.
你知道作为硬币的好处吗 韦伯斯特先生?
You know the nice thing about pennies, Mr. Webster?
它们表面刻有日期
They have dates on them.
而你可以选择日期
And you can pick the date.
你自己的日期
Your own date.
今天的日期
Today's date.
拥有一个崭新的开始
You can get a fresh start.
让自己变成一枚闪闪发光的新的硬币
You can be a brand-new shiny penny.
老实说 医生
you know, I got to be honest with you
今天刚进你办公室时  我没有任何意愿和你说话
I had no intention of--whatsoever-- talking to you once I got inside your office today,
可是我不得不承认
but I have to admit, I find therapy...
我觉得治疗...
well, it's therapeutic.
效果很好
我不太明白
I don't follow.
如果你没打算和我聊天
If you didn't plan on talking today,
那你为什么进来?
why did you come in?
嗯...我今天在车站的背面看到了 那个广告
Well, I saw the ad on the back of the bus stop today.
嗯...虽然不能完全说...
And, uh...
像照镜子一样
though it wasn't exactly like looking in the mirror,
但你不能否认
you can't deny that
我们的脸长得很像
there's a certain commonality in our visages.
我想我们长得是有点像...
I guess we do look a little bit alike...
...但我不明白
but I don't understand.
你想干嘛
What the hell you think you're doing?
喂
Hello.
格林先生吗?是的
Mr. Green? - Yes.
我是林肯·布伦斯
This is Lincoln Burrows.
照我说的做
Do exactly what I say.
你的西装外套
Your suit jacket.
把它扔到你身后的垃圾桶里
Toss it in the trash behind you.
什么?
Excuse me?
照我说的做
Do it.
好吧 我刚把我那价值2000美元的杰尼亚西装外套
All right. I just threw my $2,000 Zegna suit jacket
扔到垃圾桶里了
in the garbage.
很好
Good.
公园的另一边有个电话
There's a phone on the other side of the park.
四分钟内赶到那里
Be there in four minutes.
四...?
Four...?
快点 手机快没电了
make it quick. This cell is running out of juice.
你是对的
You were right.
他被人跟踪了?
- He's being tailed?
对
- Yeah.
我盯着呢
On it.
喂?
- yeah?
我在找一个穿衬衫的人
- I'm looking for a guy in a suit.
穿衬衫的人多着呢
Lots of guys with suits.
是我
It's me.
看到喷泉了吗?
See the fountain?
当然看到了
How could I not?
进去
Get in.
他们想毁掉麦克风 以防我们窃听
They want to drown the mics in case we bugged him.
嗨 先生
Hey, mister.
这是给你的
This is for you.
我没兴趣
- I'm not interested.
我不是想卖给你--刚刚有人给了我20美元
- I'm not selling it-- some dude gave me 20 bucks
让我把它交给我看到的第一个浑身湿透的人
to give it to the first wet guy I see.
给
Here.
看到你对面那栋楼了吗?
See the building across from you?
嗯
Yeah.
走进去
Go inside.
听着 这事变得越来越荒谬了
Look, this is getting ridiculous.
我做了所有你要求我做的事  如果你想见我...
I've done everything you've asked. If you want to meet me...
我们被耍过太多次了 格林先生
we've been burned way too many times, Mr. Green.
我们需要确保这事按照正确的 方向行进
We need to make sure that this thing goes down right.
走进楼里 把手机放在耳边
Go inside, and keep the phone to your ear.
喂
- yeah.
他在哪？ 他进贝克博物馆了
- Where are we? He's gone inside the Bbeck museum,
但我们有后援在那
but we've got men out back.
他跑不掉的
He's not going anywhere.
喂?
yeah?
去艾伯特公园.
Get to ebert park.
我在那有人盯着斯科菲尔德和布伦斯
I have men on Scofield and Burrows.
艾伯特公园?
Ebert park?
斯科菲尔德和我们监视的目标安排了一次见面
Scofield set a meet with a target we're surveilling.
斯科菲尔德在芝加哥做什么?
What the hell is Scofield doing in Chicago?
你在问鹿儿为什么走进你的圈套吗?
You're asking why the deer walked into your crosshairs?
你只要抓住这个机会 马宏
Just take the shot, Mahone.
我知道 我知道
I'm on it. I'm on it.
还有...艾力克斯
And Alex.
富兰克林
Franklin.
利用富兰克林来帮我们找到斯科菲尔德
Using Franklin to help me find Scofield.
不 我们不需要他了
We don't need him for that anymore.
我所要的只是一个没有疑点的死亡
What I do need is a death with no questions.
瞧 虽然现在还没消息 但我相信他很快就会来找我了
hey, look, it's nothing yet, man, but I'm sure he'll hit me real soon,
很快 好吗?
okay?
你看 如果我在你的位置
you know, if I were in your situation...
所有你做的事,所有你做的决定
everything you've done, every decision you've made...
我也会那样做
I'd have done the same thing.
你是个好人  好父亲
You're a good man, good father.
计划改变
There's, uh... been a change of plans.
看起来以后我不再需要你的帮助了
It looks like I'm not gonna ne your help after all.
那么 你发现了 斯科菲尔德
so you found Scofield.
我的同事们快搞定了
My colleagues are getting pretty close, yeah.
那么
- So...
那么我猜你能让我自由了
- so i guess you can set me free, then.
当然不
Of course not.
你和我我们有个交易  是不是
- you and me, we had a deal, right?
对
- Right.
我把你的妻子放出来
I get your wife released,
照顾你女儿的身体
take care of your daughter's health,
你帮我找到斯科菲尔德
you get me Scofield.
但是你你在自己抓他
But you, you're getting him yourself.
就像你说的那样 我知道
You just said that. I know.
我知道 我只想让你知道
I know. I just want you to know...
那个  嗯 我对你保证我的承诺
that, uh, I'm going to keep my promise to you
我将要帮助你的家人
and I'm going to help your family.
但是我也需要你的帮助
But I'm gonna need your help, too,
有些事你不准备做，我也不想你去做
and this is something that you're not gonna want to do and I don't want you to do this,
但是我需要你做这个
but I need you to do this
如果你不做 我会让卡茜 再次被捕的
and if you don't, I ill have Kacee arrested again,
并且我会让蒂蒂的医护停止
and I will have Dede's medical care stopped, and I will
虽然我会恨我自己 这让我觉得恶心
hate myself, and it will make me sick
但是我对上帝发誓
but I swear to god...
我会毁了他们-- 不要让我这样做
I will ruin their lives-- don't make me.
你究竟要让我做什么?
What the hell are you saying to me?
今天晚些时候  你会在你的牢房里找到一个包裹
Later today, you'll get a package in your cell.
那时我送来的 我要你用它  行吗
Its gonna be from me.I need you to use it.Okay?
好的  那里面有什么
Okay. Wht's in it?
那里面究竟有什么
What the hell is in it, man?
只要用它就行了  我希望你照做
Just use it, or you'll wish you had.
包裹里有什么
What's in the package?
包裹里到底有什么
What the hell is in the package, man?
好吧  我在大厅里
I'm in the lobby.
上你左边的楼梯
Take the stairs to your left.
上到顶 通过那个通道
When you get to the top, cross the catwalk.
好的  我正通过
Okay, I'm across.
走进大厅  下楼梯到地下室
Go down the hall, down the stairs to the basement.
通过白色的门
Go through the white door.
你左边的那个
The one on the left.
班尼特: 莎拉  我希望你会先来找我
Sara, I wish you had come to me first.
我和库伯 格林认识很久了
Cooper Green and i go way back.
如果有人能帮助迈克尔和林肯  就是他
If anyone can help Michael and Lincoln, it's him.
我能帮你吗 是
Can I help you? Yeah.
格林先生在吗
Yeah.Is Mr. Green in?
他在等你吗
Is he expecting you?
布伦斯
Bruce.
哦 太好了  你回来了
Oh, good, you're back.
我来这儿帮你
I'm here to help you.
帮我 用什么帮
Help me? With what?
斯科菲尔德和布伦斯 他们现在在哪
Scofield and Burrows. Where are they now?
这太可笑了
This is absurd.
这条隧道通向地下
This tunnel goes underground.
你已经在另一栋建筑底下了
You're already under another building.
看到你右边第二个门了吗
See the second door on your right?
是的
Yeah
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你找到了
You made it.
我很抱歉  莎拉.唐克雷蒂   我相信你今天见过
I'sorry.Sara Tancredi.
迈克尔.斯科菲尔德和林肯.布伦斯了
I-I trust you've met with Michael Scofield and Lincoln Burrows today?
如果我见过我确信我会记得
Well, I'm sure I'd remember if I did.
莎拉
Sara?
如果你是库伯.格林 那么现在谁跟迈克尔在一起
If you're Cooper Green, who's with Michael right now?
格林先生
Mr. Green?
我是迈克尔.斯科菲尔德
I'm Michael Scofield.
好啊  终于见到你太好了
Well, it's nice to finally meet you.
你  呃  你有那个录音吗?
Do you... uh, do you have the tape?
就在这里
It's right here.
喂
Yeah.
林肯  我是莎拉 听我说
Lincoln, it's Sara.Listen to me.
现在和迈克尔在一起的那个人
The man that Michael's with right now
不是库伯.格林  你听见我说了吗
is not Cooper Green, do you hear me?
那个和迈克尔在一起的人不是库伯 格林
The man that Michael's with right now is not Cooper Green.
我们得快点
We should hurry.
你在芝加哥了-- 不会太久
You're in Chicago-- it won't be long
公司就会知道你在城里
before the company knows you're in town.
你要去哪
Where are we going?
我要把录音送到
Well, we're going to make sure that
它应该在的人手里
the tape goes in the right hands.
谁
Whose?
一个朋友
A friend.
什么样的朋友
What kind of friend?
他是联邦法官
He's a federal judge.
知道这个对你来说足够了吗
Is that good enough for you?
那个录音是我哥哥的性命
This tape is my brother's life.
还有我的性命
And mine.
因此...
And consequently...
我需要知道是谁
I need a name.
斯科特. 沃伦法官
udge scott warren
迈尔斯总统任命的终身法官
a lifetime appointee who was put on the bench by president mills.
他没有必要担心失去工作 不必对莱娜斯忠诚
He has no job to lose, no loyalty to reynolds.
他想看到她消失  就像我们一样
He wants to see her gone, just like us.
好吧 我们走
Well, let's go.
我  我把车停在雕像旁边了
I-I, I left my car over by the statue.
你被跟踪了 格林先生
You were tailed, Mr. Green.
法官向我们走来了
The judge comes to us.
我准备好会面
I'll set up the meeting.
你看见我的衣服了吗
Do you see my clothes?
你的兄弟确认
Your brother made certain that
跟踪我的那个人已经不在了
anybody who was tailing me is long gone,
最主要的 我是一个哮喘症患者
and on top of that, I'm an asthmatic.
我的吸入过滤器在我的夹克口袋里
My inhaler is in my jacket pocket,
林肯让我扔了的那件衣服
which Lincoln made me throw away.
我现在好了 但是在十分钟以内
I'm okay now, but in about ten minutes,
我就会呼吸困难
I' gonna have a hard time breathing.
我有一个备用的在我的手套盒子里
I've got a spare in my glove box,
所以我们
so could we please
得回到我的车里去
just get back to my car?
我的车只有几个街区远
My car is just a few blocks away.
沙丁胺醇(支气管扩张药)   Cortizaid(药名) 还是 Prednizone(药名)
Albuterol, Cortizaid or Prednizone?
什么
What?
我的妈妈有哮喘症
My mother was an asthmatic.
你的吸入过滤器里用的是哪种药
What do you use in your inhaler?
它们都有什么区别
What the hell difference does it make?
先回答我  快点
Just answer the question, please.
你真是很麻烦  你知道吗
You're a real piece of work, you know that?
我向你证明过我自己多少遍了
How many times I got to prove myself to you?
只有一次
Just one.
好吧.Cortizaid(支气管药)
fine. Uh... Cortizaid.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
只是...
It's just,
如果你知道  如果你知道我们经历了什么...
uh... if you knew what,
我明白
I understand.
我们现在能不能  求你了
Can we now just, please
到我的车里去?好吧.
go to my car? Yeah.
单程票到 曼谷 劳驾.
One-way ticket to Bangkok, s'il vous plait.
哦 对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
我们今天的航班都满了
We don't have anything until tomorrow.
不过如果你不介意中途在
Unless you don't mind taking
芝加哥和另一个国际机场转机的话 我们还有一些空位
a few connections through Chicago, and there's one more international stop.
哪个越早起飞 我就要哪个
Whatever leaves first.
好的
Okay.
请出示你证件
I.D., Please.
好 斯塔..莫尔 先生？
Okay, mister...Stammel?
哦，是斯塔莫尔医生
Oh, it's, uh, it's Doctor Stammel
也谢谢你 好的
and thank you. All right
请稍等片刻
it'll be just a few minutes.
先生 我来帮你拖运这个行李
I'll check this bag for you, sir.
不不 这个行李我随身带着 还给我
Oh, no, that's coming with me. Give it back.
先生 这个行李对于随机携带已经超重了
Sir, I know that bag is way over the weight limit for carry-on.
不管是存放在飞机的货舱里还是飞机上
What difference does a few extra pounds make on a three-ton aircraft,
这小小的几磅对一个三吨重的飞机来说算得了什么
whether that's up above or underneath?
这违反了联邦航空局的规定
It's an faa violation.
先生 你的行李保证不会有问题或损坏
Sir, your bag will be safe.
今天 这个多风的城市对旅游者来说
Today will be a tough day for travelers
可能会不太顺利 为了迎接莱娜斯总统
in the windy city as all streets
只要在西博恩酒店六条街 半径之内的每一条街
In a six-block radius of the seaburn hotel
都会被关闭
have been closed to traffic
莱娜斯总统今晚将会在西博恩酒店做出演讲
in Anticipation of president Reynolds's speech there this evening.
这是莱娜斯在中西部加强 她竞选总统的其中一个站点
This'll be one of several midwestern stops for the president
听着 狄欧 我知道你是新来的
Hey, Theo, i know you're new
但是在这里记事本我们两面都用的 知道吗？
but we use both sides of legal pads in this office, okay?
除了循环之外 我们还得节省
Before we recycle, we reduce.
如果克曼奇族能把整头水牛的每一处都用上
The comanche used the entire buffalo.
那我们也行
So can we.
其实呢 大部分的克曼奇族都会
Actually, a majority of tribes would farm land till
耕田种植直到农场不能用为止
it was stripped of its utility,
然后他们将会离开(即他们不会循环的意思)
then they'd just...move on.
印第安人保护自然的想法
conservationist is a myth
是这些白人因为罪恶感 编出来的谎言
created by white liberal guilt.
保罗
Paul.
好啊 克里斯丁
Hi, Kristine.
我本来希望
I'd hoped
能在爸爸的葬礼上看到你的
maybe I'd see you at dad's funeral.
那个男人在心跳停止前已经死了
That man died long before his heart stopped.
那个葬礼只是一个仪式
That funeral was a formality.
那样说是不公平的
That's really not fair.
这是事实
It's true.
那....
So...
你想知道妈妈现在如何吗？
you want to know how mom is?
就算她把我从肚子里生出来
Just 'cause someone spits you out of your crotch
这并不代表她有资格做我的母亲
doesn't make them your mother.
那女人是个疯子
That woman is insane.
你还记得吗？
Do you remember?
你都忘记了吗？
Have you suppressed it all?
我知道 保罗 不像你
I know, Paul.
我每天都曾经历
I was there every day...unlike you.
我熬了十八年
I was there for 18 years.
但是你离开了
Then you just left.
那时我才十岁 保罗
I was ten, Paul.
你是我这世界上的唯一剩下的亲人 可是...
You were all I had in the world, and...
你就把我丢在那儿
you just left me there.
对不起
I'm sorry.
如果可以话 我愿意把你一起带着
If I could have taken you with me, I would have,
我每天都挂念着你
and I've thought about you every day.
不再是你记忆中的那个哥哥
I'm not the brother you remember.
我变了...
I've changed...
走进了...
in A...
一个不归途
really bad way.
呃...
Uh...
到一个连我自己都分不清
to the point where I don't know
好或坏的地步
what good or bad is anymore,
我要去解决一件事.
and I am going to do something--
我必须解决那件事...但是这件事会让很多人
I have to do something...
感觉到极度可恨的 保罗
that a lot of people are going to think is horrible.  Paul.
我只要你记着
And you just remember...
和你一起长大的哥哥
the brother you grew up with.
你只要记得他就行了
You just remember him.
你是我的妹妹 克里斯丁 我会永远爱着你
You're my sister You're my sister
我被打晕了
I was out cold.
我不知道我们去哪了
I don't know where they went.
那把你叫到芝加哥中心
And it was their idea for you to meet them here
见面的也是他们？
in the middle of Chicago?
嗯
Yeah.
我的天哪
oh, man.
马宏
Mahone.
他们已经走了
You brought me in too late They're gone.
那就把他们找出来
then find them.
让我把这件事搞清楚
Let me get this straight.
这兄弟俩回到了一个
The brothers come back to a city that's 15 miles
离福克斯河不到十五个英里的城市
from the prison they escaped from.
他们为了什么要这样做呢?
Why would they do that?
有可能是因为总统要在芝加哥
Maybe it's because the president is
发表演讲 他们说不定有什么计划
in Chicago to make a speech, and they're up to something
这更是另一个我们要找到 他们的原因
which is why we need to find them
在所有人之中他们为什么偏偏要见
And of all people, they want to meet with somebody
律政署里的人呢？
from the attorney general's office?
你想说什么？
Your point?
布伦斯是无辜的
Burrows is innocent.
哇 你真的很厉害 亚历山大
Wow, you're good, Alex.
就跟广告上说的一样
As advertised.
没有人是真正无辜的
No one's truly innocent.
所有人里面 你应该最清楚
You of all people should know that.
肯定是那个接待员
it must have been the receptionist.
她是唯一一个和我对过话的人
She's the only one I spoke to.
迈克尔·斯科菲尔德 库泊 格林
Michael Scofield. Cooper Green.
我们一定要在小孩长大之前
We got to get as much of that in
抓紧时间多做一点 好好享受
as possible before the baby gets here.
为什么
0Why?
因为一旦小孩开始慢慢长大了
Because, once the baby's growing in there,
在做的话就感觉有点不对了
doesn't it just get kind of wrong?
也是啊
Oh, yeah.
哇 怎么了？
- Whoa. - What?
我刚刚感觉到小孩在动了
I just felt the baby move.
费尔南多 那是不可能的 那简直太早了...
Fernando, that's impossible-- it's a little too early...
我绝对感觉到了
I know what I just felt.
医生的确有说过  在某种活动之后
Well, the doctor did say that
小孩有可能会开始动
he can become active after certain activities.
哇！你感觉到了没有？
Whoa!Did you feel that?
嗯,有点微动 什么微动
Yeah, like a flutter. Flutter my ass.
他好健壮
He's strong.
他将会是国家足球队的队长
He's going to be the captain of the national soccer team.
你听到了 宝贝？
You hear that, junior?
只要一你出世...
As soon as you're born,
我就要把足球放到你手里
I' putting a soccer ball in your hands.
不 他将会拿起书本
No, he's going to have books.
那好 有关足球的书籍
Fine. Books about soccer.
看吧 宝贝
See, baby.
我和你说一切都会没事的
I told you everything was going to work out.
我们在一个别人都找不到地方
We're out in the middle of nowhere,
小孩也很好
baby's doing great.
一切都会变得很完美
Everything's going to be perfect.
看起来前面是一片晴空
Well, it looks like we've got nothing but smooth skies ahead,
我们应该会准时
so we should be arriving in Mexico right on time.
抵达墨西哥 不好意思
Excuse me.
餐食什么时候才会送来？我都饿死了
When's the meal coming around? I'm starved.
为了降低票价
As a way to keep ticket prices low,
正餐已经不再列入我们的服务套餐当中
we have removed the in-flight meal frm our service package.
服务套餐里面还剩下什么?
What's left on the service package?
椒盐卷饼和一些零食
retzels and bags of krispity krunch.
要椒盐卷饼
Pretzels.
稍等片刻
Just a few minutes
有空就帮我满上  亲爱的
Freshen me up when you get a chance, darlin'.
好的马上就来  斯塔莫尔医生
Right away, dr.Stammel.
迪迪现在很好
Dede's doing real good.
药品很见效  她开始能吃东西了
She's responding to the meds, um, eating.
她会没事的
he's going to be okay.
因为有你在
Because of you.
因为有你在  她就会好起来的
She's going to be okay because of you.
我想知道...
I need to know...
...你是否已经原谅我
that you forgive me.
我当然原谅你的  我明白的
I know that. Of course I forgive you.
你不知道在迪迪四岁的时候
You know when Dede was like four,
有一次她想看电视
she wanted to watch this video.
我跟她不耐烦地说
And I kept telling her you know,
等我看完比赛
"after the game,
等我看完比赛  好么?
after the game, okay?”
她就一直不断的问啊问
She kept asking and kept asking,
后来我实在不耐烦了  训斥了她几句
and I lost my patience and I snapped at her.
很不耐烦的训斥
I snapped at her real bad.
她躲到角落里...
She went over into the corner, and...
我都没有过去安慰她
I didn't even go over and say anything.
你为何这样耿耿于怀
Why are you getting yourself upset over
这事都过去好几年了
something that happened years ago, baby?
- 迪迪爱你的- 亲爱的  听我说
Dede loves you.
为我做件事
Baby, I want you to do something for me.
替我告诉她
I want you to tell her that
我对不起她
I'm sorry.
我实在对不起她
I'm so sorry.
我的宝贝女儿对我来说
And that my baby girls
她就是我的一切  告诉她
means everything to me
她就是我的一切  好吗?
I want you to tell her that she means everything to me, okay?
你要每天都告诉她
- You tell her that every day.
- 时间到了  - 无论发生什么...
-Time.- No matter what...
女士
- a'am...
告诉她  告诉她  好吗?
tell her.Tell her, okay?
不论发生什么 你要向我承诺  好吗?
No matter what, you promise that, okay?
- 女士  - 请你告诉她
Please, please, you got to tell her.
- 你必须告诉她...  - 好
You have to tell her... okay, okay.
女士
Ma'am.
你真的必须走了
You really have to go.
告诉她
Tell her, tell her.
好的
Ok
请注意
Attentn, attention.
所有参观者必须站在护栏之外
All spectators must remain behind the barricades
随时保持秩序
at all times.
总统将马上抵达
The president will be arriving shortly.
任何人企图穿越护栏将...
Anyone attempting to circumvent the barricades...
半个街区以南发现一名爆炸犯
whoa..Got a boom charlie half block south.
队长叫你马上过去
Team leader wants you there right now.
什么型号的?
What's the M.O.?
简易炸弹绑在了他的...
He's got an tied strapped to...
他特地要你来这个喷泉处
he asked you to come to this fountainpecifically?
是
Yeah.
我看一下公园地图
Let me take a look at that park map.
为什么不是公园东边的喷泉处
Why not the fountain on the east side of the park?
这边离电话亭最近
ecause this one's closer to the pay phone he called me on.
不  是因为这里离他们最近
No, because this one's closer to them.
他们告诉你在雕塑那边见
They tell you to meet them at the statue.
然后是喷泉
Then the fountain.
然后把你带入那座楼
Then they send you to the building
公园的对面
across the park.
为什么
Why?
他们把你放在视线范围之内
'Cause they want to keep you in their sights.
是为了观察你的行踪
Because they're watching you.
但是从哪里?
But from where?
雕塑  喷泉  楼房...
Statue, fountain, building...
在那
there.
那个酒店
the hotel
你清楚拿到了什么
You know what you have?
我想我们很明白
I think we have a pretty good idea.
你在干什么
What you doing?
从这个U盘里提取特殊数据
Getting all unique data from the memory key
这样我们可以鉴别它的唯一性
so we can identify this key from any other--
然后开始记录下里面的保存信息
label it, start a proper record of a chain of
再把这些交给我信任的法官
custody to present to the judges I trust.
不
no.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
记忆库的时间不对
No, it's the date stamp on the memory key.
这是复制的数据
It's the copy date.
我没听清  这是什么?
I'm sorry, what's that?
日期是这鬼东西被复制的时间
It's the date the damn thing was copied,
而不是
not the date
谈话的原始日期
that the conversation was originally recorded.
那又怎么样
So what?
你已经听过了这录音的内容
I mean, you heard what was on the tape.
没有确凿的时间标注
Without a time stamp of exactly
关于这段谈话
when this conversation took place,
我们无法确认斯蒂德曼
we can't prove that this is Terrence Steadman talking
是在你被指控谋杀之前所录下的
after you supposedly killed him.
因为这可以被认作是
This could have happened a year
他葬礼一年之后的录音
before his funeral.
因为这无法鉴别
No, it can't be authenticated,
所以不能成为呈堂证供
so it can't be admitted to any court as evidence.
人们为了它而死
People died because of this.
我的家人
My family died.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
从法律上来讲  这段录音没有任何意义
Legally speaking, this tape is useless.
亚历山大马宏FBI
Alexander Mahone, FBI.
这两个人有没有来过?
Have either of these men checked in?
我没见过他们
No, not that i've seen.
这名女士呢?
What about this woman?
恩
Yeah.
10-06房间
Room 10-06.
10-06  谢谢
10-06,Thank you.
这不是结束
It's not over.
- 我们就差一步  - 你说过都没问题的
We're this close.
我说了这没办法使你们
You already said it's done.
在法庭上洗脱罪名
Actually, I said it couldn't help exonerate you in a court of law.
不过在法律之外  它会对你们有利的
Maybe it can help you outside the law.
如何?
How?
我们都听了这段谈话
Well, we all heard the conversation.
证明林肯清白的潜在的证据
There's more to this tape than
可能比录音本身更重要
poential proof of Lincoln's innocence.
关于凯若琳雷诺德的罪证
here is proof of caroline reynold's guilt.
在我们手中
Guilt about something that she does not
这罪证是她不愿被任何人所了解的
want anyone to know anything about.
我们勒索她
So we blackmail her.
我是法庭官员
I'm an officer of the court.
我不能这么说
I...i didn't say that.
以勒索换来什么?
Blackmail in exchange for what?
总统的宽恕
A presidential pardon.
那女人陷害了我...
The woman that set me up...
要让我获得自由
is going to set me free.
我想她会亲手签字的
I think she'll sign it with her own hand.
A组B组  我是队长
Ace team, beta team -- this is leader one.
那位女士将在两分钟过后抵达目的地
The squaw will reach home base in T minus two minutes.
我爱你
I love you.